<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>vitalyart.aula-f75-max-driver</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <pkgname>aula-f75-max-driver</pkgname>

  <name>Aula F75 Max Driver</name>
  <summary>Configure the Epomaker x Aula F75 Max keyboard</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Настраивайте клавиатуру Epomaker x Aula F75 Max</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Configura el teclado Epomaker x Aula F75 Max</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uz">Epomaker x Aula F75 Max klaviaturasini sozlang</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="kk">Epomaker x Aula F75 Max пернетақтасын баптаңыз</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Configure o teclado Epomaker x Aula F75 Max</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-Hans">配置 Epomaker x Aula F75 Max 键盘</summary>

  <developer id="vitalyart">
    <name>VitalyArt</name>
  </developer>

  <description>
    <p>
      Aula F75 Max Driver is a native Linux utility for configuring the
      Epomaker x Aula F75 Max keyboard display, RGB lighting, battery status,
      response level, sleep timeout, Game Mode, and HID diagnostics.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">
      Aula F75 Max Driver - нативная Linux-утилита для настройки клавиатуры
      Epomaker x Aula F75 Max: дисплея, RGB-подсветки, батареи, отклика,
      sleep timeout, Game Mode и диагностики HID.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="es">
      Aula F75 Max Driver es una utilidad nativa para Linux que configura el
      teclado Epomaker x Aula F75 Max: pantalla, iluminación RGB, batería,
      nivel de respuesta, suspensión, Game Mode y diagnóstico HID.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="uz">
      Aula F75 Max Driver - Epomaker x Aula F75 Max klaviaturasi displeyi, RGB
      yoritishi, batareyasi, javob darajasi, uyqu vaqti, Game Mode va HID
      diagnostikasini sozlash uchun native Linux utilitasi.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="kk">
      Aula F75 Max Driver - Epomaker x Aula F75 Max пернетақтасының дисплейін,
      RGB жарығын, батареясын, жауап деңгейін, ұйқы уақытын, Game Mode режимін
      және HID диагностикасын баптауға арналған native Linux утилитасы.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">
      Aula F75 Max Driver é um utilitário nativo para Linux que configura o
      teclado Epomaker x Aula F75 Max: tela, RGB, bateria, nível de resposta,
      suspensão, Game Mode e diagnóstico HID.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-Hans">
      Aula F75 Max Driver 是一款原生 Linux 工具，用于配置 Epomaker x Aula F75 Max
      键盘屏幕、RGB 灯效、电池状态、响应等级、睡眠时间、Game Mode 和 HID 诊断。
    </p>
    <p>
      The app communicates directly through Linux hidraw and hidapi, installs
      the required udev rule, and separates wired USB-C display workflows from
      2.4G receiver settings.
    </p>
    <ul>
      <li>Upload PNG, JPEG, GIF, BMP, TIFF, and WebP images to the 128 x 128 keyboard display.</li>
      <li>Control RGB lighting mode, brightness, speed, direction, fixed color, response level, and sleep timeout.</li>
      <li>Read battery percentage through the 2.4G receiver and inspect HID endpoints for troubleshooting.</li>
    </ul>
  </description>

  <launchable type="desktop-id">aula-f75-max-driver.desktop</launchable>
  <icon type="stock">aula-f75-max-driver</icon>
  <provides>
    <binary>AulaF75MaxDriverLinux</binary>
    <id>aula-f75-max-driver.desktop</id>
  </provides>

  <categories>
    <category>Settings</category>
    <category>HardwareSettings</category>
  </categories>

  <keywords>
    <keyword>Aula</keyword>
    <keyword>F75</keyword>
    <keyword>Keyboard</keyword>
    <keyword>HID</keyword>
    <keyword>RGB</keyword>
  </keywords>

  <url type="homepage">https://vitalyart.github.io/Aula-F75-Max-Driver/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/VitalyArt/Aula-F75-Max-Driver/issues</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/VitalyArt/Aula-F75-Max-Driver</url>

  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Main Aula F75 Max Driver window</caption>
      <image type="source">https://vitalyart.github.io/Aula-F75-Max-Driver/screenshots/main-window.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>HID endpoint diagnostics and app settings</caption>
      <image type="source">https://vitalyart.github.io/Aula-F75-Max-Driver/screenshots/details-window.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>

  <releases>
    <release version="1.0.0" date="2026-07-16" />
  </releases>

  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
</component>
